<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DESFire EV3 SUN feature</string>
    <string name="app_version">0.0.1</string>
    <string name="home_description">This application enables the Secure Unique NFC (SUN) feature available on Mifare DESFire EV3 tags</string>
    <string name="home_fragments">There are 5 icons to click on:\n
        1 home = this page\n
        2 read = reads the NDEF message on the tag with and without authentication\n
        3 prepare = run all necessary steps to activate SUN feature\n
        4 activate = enables and disables the SUN feature (mirroring of data)\n
        5 format = formats the PICC for a clean workspace\n\n
        Note: This app is working with tag type Mifare DESFire EV3 only !</string>

    <!-- strings for prepare sun/sdm -->
    <string name="header_prepare_sdm">Prepares the tag to use the SUN/SDM feature</string>
    <string name="description_prepare_sdm">Prepares the tag by creating a new application, creating a Standard File to take the NDEF Container File (CC) and a Standard File that stores the template URL (NDEF Data File).</string>
    <string name="warning_prepare_tag">WARNING: The app will IMMEDIATELY write to an attached tag without any further confirmation !</string>
    <string name="more_information_prepare_sdm">More Information about the application and file creations:\n
    1) The app will create a new application with applicationID 010000 and ISO application name D2760000850101,
    this is necessary for NDEF workflow. The app will have 5 AES based application keys. There are no restrictions on file and directory handling.\n
    2) In the new application a new Standard File is created with a size of 32 bytes that holds the NDEF Container File.\n
    The file number is 01 and the ISO fileId is E103h, the Communication mode is Plain,
    Access rights: Read &amp; Write key: E, CAR key: E, Read key: E, Write key: E (E means free access without any authentication)\n
    3) A second Standard File is created in the application with a sie of 256 bytes that hold the template URL for the NDEF Link record.\n
    The file number is 02 and the ISO fileId is E104h, the Communication mode is Plain,
    Access rights: Read &amp; Write key: E, CAR key: 0, Read key: E, Write key: E (E means free access without any authentication)
    </string>

    <!-- strings for activate sun/sdm -->
    <string name="header_activate_sdm">Activate the SUN feature by enabling Secure Dynamic Messaging (SDM)</string>
    <string name="description_activate_sdm">Activates the mirroring of data (UID, read counter, secret file data and MAC) in a NDEF message on tapping.\n\nThis is working on Mifare DESFire EV3 tags only.</string>
    <string name="description_activate_sdm_rg">choose your action on SUN/SDM feature</string>

    <!-- strings for read ndef content -->
    <string name="header_read_ndef_content">Read the NDEF content</string>
    <string name="description_read_ndef_content">Reads the content of the NDEF Data File (2) and displays the content in hex and string encoding</string>
    <string name="description_read_ndef_content_rg">select authenticate mode</string>

    <!-- strings for format picc -->
    <string name="header_format_picc">Format the PICC</string>
    <string name="description_format_picc">Formatting the PICC will delete all applications and files on the PICC and releases all storage space back to factory settings.\n
    The settings of the Master Application are not reset so if you changed the default Master Application Key and key settings these changes will remain.</string>
    <string name="warning_format_picc">WARNING: The app will IMMEDIATELY FORMAT the PICC when attached without any further confirmation !\n\n
    You will loose any applications and files on the PICC without receovery !</string>
    <string name="more_information_format_picc">Formatting the PICC will release all storage space back to factory settings.\n
    The settings of the Master Application are not reset so if you changed the default Master Application Key and/or key settings these changes will remain.\n\n
    The app will authenticate with the DEFAULT Master Application Key first to run the format PICC command.</string>



    <string name="header_read">This app reads an NDEF message</string>
    <string name="description_read">This example expects a class 4 type tag with an NDEF record (RTD_TEXT).\n\nWhen a tag is discovered the data from all records will be read.</string>
    <string name="nfc_result">NFC read result</string>
    <string name="action_licenses">Used material and their licenses</string>
    <string name="header_ndef_settings">NDEF message settings</string>
    <string name="description_ndef_settings">Writes the NDEF message template to the NTAG with defined placeholders for UID, read counter and MAC.\n\nThis is working on tag types NTAG213, 215 or 216 only.</string>
    <string name="description_ndef_settings_2">There are 2 steps to do:\n1. press the TEST AND SAVE NDEF SETTINGS button\n2. tap a NTAG21x tag to the reader</string>
    <string name="header_activate">Activate the mirroring of data to NDEF message</string>
    <string name="description_activate">Activates the mirroring of data (UID, read counter and MAC) in an NDEF message on tapping</string>
    <string name="description_activate_rg">choose your action</string>
    <string name="header_personalize_tag">Run all steps to personalize a tag for NDEF mirroring</string>
    <string name="description_personalize_tag">This are the steps that will run when a tag is tapped\n\n1. write the NDEF template to the tag\n2. disable all existing mirror\n3. enable UID mirroring\n4. write the UID-based MAC to the tag</string>
    <string name="warning_personalize_tag">The app will IMMEDIATELY write to an attached tag without any further confirmation !</string>

</resources>